Select Page

Privacy Policy
==============

At Shape Technologies Group, Inc.(the “Company”), we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to respond to your requests for information, to process orders, to improve our products and to communicate with you about promotions and items that we think may be of interest to you. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

**What information do we collect? How do we use it?**

When you use a computer, tablet, smart phone or other device to access our websites or purchase an item via our online properties, we may collect information about the device and how you use it.

You may be issued a “cookie,” which helps track your session while online. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive. Among other things, cookies help to make your site visit more relevant. We use cookies to see which areas and features are popular and to track site visits. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you may set your browser to refuse cookies or alert you when cookies are being sent; however, it is possible that some parts of our sites will not function properly if you do so.

When you request information, we need to know your name, company name, e-mail address, phone number, and mailing address. If you purchase an item from us, we also need your credit card number and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. Data processing occurs in the United States and European Union.

**How do we protect customer information?**

We use customer data to process orders, to improve our products and to communicate with you about promotions and items that we think may be of interest to you. We take commercially reasonable measures to protect customer data against unauthorized access.

The Company may share customer data with its subsidiaries or affiliates, which may use this information for all purposes outlined in this privacy policy. The Company is permitted to transfer this information, in whole or in part, in connection with a merger, change of control or sale of all or part of the Company’s business. By using any of the Company’s websites, you consent to the collection and use of this information by the Company and its subsidiaries and affiliates. The Company may change its privacy policy from time to time, and at the Company’s sole discretion.

23500 64th Ave S  
Kent, WA 98032  
(253) 246-3200

©2024 Shape Technologies Group. All Rights Reserved. [Privacy Policy](https://www.shapetechnologies.com/privacy-policy/)
